A Guide to the Thomas Inge papers, 1879-2001
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series II - Other Literary Materials and Personal Items
  - Subseries B - Personal Items
    - Other:
      - Society for the Study of Midwestern Literature, 1982-1983 (Box 69)
      - Southeastern American Studies Association Newsletter, 1981 (Box 69)
      - Southern Partisan, The, 1982 (Box 69)
      - Tennessee Historical Quarterly, 1971 (Box 69)
      - Thomas Wolfe Review, The, 1987 (Box 69)
      - Touchstone, 1986 (Box 69)
      - University College Quarterly, 1980 (Box 69)
      - University Publishing, 1979 (Box 69)
      - Victorian Society in American, 1980 (Box 69)
      - Young Adult Literature: Background and Criticism, 1980 (Box 69)
      - Bulletin of Randolph-Macon College, 1954-1959 (Box 70)
      - Cahill & Company: a Feast of Favorite Authors, undated (Box 70)
      - Circumnavigator's Club, 1985 (Box 70)
      - Clemson University News, 1980 (Box 70)
      - Clemson World, 1984 (Box 70)
      - Co-Evolution Quarterly, 1979 (Box 70)
      - Graduate English Newsletter Vanderbilt University, 1976, 1977, 1981 (Box 70)
      - Journal of Irreproducible Results, 1988 (Box 70)
      - Lost Generation Journal, undated, 1973 (Box 70)
      - Museum of the Confederacy Newsletter, 1982 (Box 70)
      - Newsletter Information for the Faculty & Staff of Clemson University, 1981 (Box 70)
      - Randolph-Macon Alumni Bulletin, 1962, 1963, 1967 (Box 70)
      - Randolph-Macon: Bulletin of Randolph-Macon College, 1980, 1985 (Box 70)
      - R-MC: Bulletin of Randolph-Macon College, 1983, 1984 (Box 70)
      - Stylus, The - Randolph-Macon College, 1957, 1965, 1966 (Box 70)
      - Vanderbilt Alumnus, 1961, 1973, 1981 (Box 70)
      - Vugenl, 1980 (Box 70)
      - Yellow Jacket, The, 1961 (Box 70)
      - Battlefield Park High School: The Battlefield Annual, 1958 (Box 71)
      - Biology 10 Notebook 1 of 2, 1956 (Box 71)
      - Biology 10 Notebook 2 of 2, 1956 (Box 71)
      - John Marshall Corps of Cadets: Orders, Memoranda, and TRNG. Schedules, Fall Term 1954-1955 (Box 71)
      - Randolph Macon College: The Yellow Jacket, 1958 (Box 71)
  - Sub-series C - Photographs
    - Captains of the John Marshall High School Corps of Cadets, 1954 (Box 72)
    - Caron, Lesile (Box 72)
    - Early Comic Panel Proofs, 1904 - 1907, 1914, 1916 (Box 72)
    - Exhibition "The American Comic Strip: Its History and Development" negatives (Box 72)
    - Exhibition "The American Comic Strip: Its History and Development" proofs (Box 72)
    - Exhibition "The American Comic Strip: Its History and Development" photographs 1of 2 (Box 72)
    - Exhibition "The American Comic Strip: Its History and Development" photographs 2 of 2 (Box 72)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs and Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 72)
    - Project Photograph, Breech, Ernest R., 1957 (Box 72)
    - Project Photograph, Dabney, Virginius, 1957 (Box 72)
    - Project Photograph, Halto, Jimmy, 1957 (Box 72)
    - Project Photograph, Schick, Dr. Béla, 1957 (Box 72)
    - Publisher Promotional Photographs, Crane, Stephen, undated (Box 72)
    - Publisher Promotional Photographs, Faulkner, William, undated (Box 72)
    - Publisher Promotional Photographs, Fitzgerald, F. Scott, undated (Box 72)
    - Publisher Promotional Photographs, Frazetta, Frank, 1975 (Box 72)
    - Publisher Promotional Photographs, Frost, Robert, undated (Box 72)
    - Publisher Promotional Photographs, Gish, Dorothy & Lillian, undated (Box 72)
    - Publisher Promotional Photographs, Hemingway, Ernest, undated (Box 72)
    - Publisher Promotional Photographs, Joyce, James, n .d. (Box 72)
    - Publisher Promotional Photographs, Mencken, H. L., undated (Box 72)
    - Publisher Promotional Photographs, Miscellaneous (6 folders), undated (Box 72)
    - Publisher Promotional Photographs, Rockwell, Norman, undated (Box 72)
    - Publisher Promotional Photographs, Woolf, Virginia, undated (Box 72)